<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>8k Plays - 8kplays</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://8kplays.ml/feeds/8kplays.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://8kplays.ml/</id><updated>2021-01-07T15:23:00+05:30</updated><entry><title>Famous Archery Quotes You Want To Know</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/archery-quotes.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-01-07T15:23:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-01-07T15:23:00+05:30</updated><author><name>8kplays</name></author><id>tag:8kplays.ml,2021-01-07:/archery-quotes.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Archery is not just a bow and arrow. It is much more than that. It's as old as mankind. It teaches us to be the focus and patient in our life. Below you can find some famous archery quotes to inspire you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Archery Inspirational Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The history of the bow …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Archery is not just a bow and arrow. It is much more than that. It's as old as mankind. It teaches us to be the focus and patient in our life. Below you can find some famous archery quotes to inspire you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Archery Inspirational Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The history of the bow and arrow is the history of mankind. - Fred Bear&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Archery does not get difficult or hard to understand until the arrow misses. - Milan E. Elott&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A good archer is known not by his arrows but by his aim. - Thomas Fuller&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The worst thing is to try to shoot as well as your previous shot. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Archery is a feeling you can’t explain. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not about being the best. It’s about being better than you were yesterday. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But you must be patient and careful; nor should you expect to become an accomplished archer without long and severe training. - Maurice Thompson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The archer that shoots badly has a lie ready. - Spanish Proverb&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing clears a troubled mind better than shooting a bow. - Fred Bear&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have to relax when you’re shooting an arrow. You can’t be tense. And that just helps, in your day-to-day life. - Stephen Amell&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you are a beginning, intermediate, or even advanced archer, Archery will give you something that’s almost impossible to find elsewhere. - Usa Archery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other archers are not my competition. I stand with them, not against them. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An arrow is never afraid of shooting from the bow; but it is afraid of not reaching the target! - Mehmet Murat ildan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even as the archer loves the arrow that flies, so too he loves the bow that remains constant in his hands. - Nigerian Proverb&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I shoot an arrow into the air, where it lands I do not care: I get my arrows wholesale! - Curly Howard&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Short Archery Quotes for Instagram&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Draw not your bow till your arrow is fixed. - English Proverbs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the long run, you only hit what you aim at. - Henry Thoreau&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t wear bows. I shoot them. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Archery requires very sensitive muscles. - Im Dong-Hyun&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No shot is hard to make, it’s just easier to miss. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Forget the last arrow only the next will count. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don’t shoot you don’t understand. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Archery is not just a sports. Its a life skill. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep Calm and Shoot Straight. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no excellence in archery without great labour. - Maurice Thompson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An archer cannot hit the bullseye if he doesn’t know where the target is. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don’t shoot fast. Shoot good. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/swimming-quotes.html"&gt;Next&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="archery"></category><category term="archery"></category><category term="bow"></category><category term="arrow"></category></entry><entry><title>The best 25+ swimming quotes that you will love</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/swimming-quotes.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-01-06T20:58:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-01-06T20:58:00+05:30</updated><author><name>8kplays</name></author><id>tag:8kplays.ml,2021-01-06:/swimming-quotes.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Swimming is a full-body workout that's why it has great benefits for our health. Here are some best swimming quotes that will help inspire you for it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Inspirational swimming quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The man who is swimming against the stream knows the strength of it. - Woodrow Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A huge part of swimming …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Swimming is a full-body workout that's why it has great benefits for our health. Here are some best swimming quotes that will help inspire you for it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Inspirational swimming quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The man who is swimming against the stream knows the strength of it. - Woodrow Wilson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A huge part of swimming for me is I love it, and it is so much fun. - Missy Franklin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you prepare for something, it's like jumping into cold water, but you're prepared. You jump in. And you start swimming, or if you don't swim, you drown. - Rza&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The water is your friend…..you don’t have to fight with water, just share the same spirit as the water, and it will help you move. - Alexander Popov&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was so surprised. Then again, I was so relaxed in the water, it felt amazing. - Pieter van den Hoogenband&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A huge part of swimming for me is I love it, and it is so much fun. - Missy Franklin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The water doesn’t know how old you are. - Dara Torres&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm just a simple guy swimming in a sea of sharks. - Don Johnson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Swimming is a confusing sport, because sometimes you do it for fun, and other times you do it to not die. And when I'm swimming, sometimes I'm not sure which one it is. - Demetri Martin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I concentrate on preparing to swim my race and let the other swimmers think about me, not me about them. - Amanda Beard&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Funny swimming quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only when the tide goes out do you discover who's been swimming naked. - Warren Buffett&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have often wanted to drown my troubles, but I can't get my wife to go swimming. - Jimmy Carter&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;we swim because we are too sexy for a sport that requires clothes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's amazing how I spend most of my day half-naked, around everyone and it's just NATURAL.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Always behave like a duck. Keep calm and unruffled on the surface, but paddle like hell underwater.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don't have to swim faster than the shark. I just need to swim faster than you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If swimming is so good for your figure, how do you explain whales?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Swimming pools quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We don't swim in your toilet, so don't pee in our pool&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This life is like a swimming pool. You dive into the water, but you can't see how deep it is. - Dennis Rodman&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think everybody pees in the pool. It's kind of a normal thing to do for swimmers. - Michael Phelps&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This life is like a swimming pool. You dive into the water, but you can't see how deep it is. - Dennis Rodman&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No one learns to swim in the shallow end of the pool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Quotes by michael phelps&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to be the best, you have to do things that other people aren't willing to do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can't put a limit on anything. The more you dream, the farther you get.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Swimming is normal for me. I'm relaxed. I'm comfortable, and I know my surroundings. It's my home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's cool just because I've had this dream of changing the sport of swimming and it's finally happening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I didn't swim my best, I'd think about it at school, at dinner, with my friends. It would drive me crazy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have the opportunity to be part of swimming history. To take the sport to a new level would be an honor for me. There's no better time to try this than now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to continue the sport of swimming. I'm not going to give up until I think it's reached where I want it to go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/sports-quotes-for-motivation.html"&gt;Next&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="swimming"></category><category term="swimming"></category><category term="swimming pool"></category></entry><entry><title>Most Powerful Sports Quotes for Motivation</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/sports-quotes-for-motivation.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-11-23T08:47:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-11-23T08:47:00+05:30</updated><author><name>8kplays</name></author><id>tag:8kplays.ml,2020-11-23:/sports-quotes-for-motivation.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Sports are the most important part of our life. We all play many sports in our life. Some are for fun or others find their life in it. While doing that sometimes we need to get the motivation to play more or to overcome our failure. For those time sports …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Sports are the most important part of our life. We all play many sports in our life. Some are for fun or others find their life in it. While doing that sometimes we need to get the motivation to play more or to overcome our failure. For those time sports quotes for motivation make a lot of help. With them, we get motivation and learn that failure is just part of success. Sometimes we just need to do hard work and never ever quit trying. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Sports Quotes for Motivation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There may be people that have more talent than you, but there’s no excuse for anyone to work harder than you do. – Derek Jeter&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To uncover your true potential you must first find your own limits and then you have to have the courage to blow past them. – Picabo Street&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is not the size of a man but the size of his heart that matters. – Evander Holyfield&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not whether you get knocked down; it’s whether you get up. – Vince Lombardi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Never give up! Failure and rejection are only the first step to succeeding. – Jim Valvano&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can’t put a limit on anything. The more you dream, the farther you get. – Michael Phelps&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Champions keep playing until they get it right. – Billie Jean King&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I never worry about the problem. I worry about the solution. – Shaquille O’Neal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve learned that something constructive comes from every defeat. – Tom Landry&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He who is not courageous enough to take risks will accomplish nothing in life. – Muhammad Ali&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can motivate by fear, and you can motivate by reward. But both those methods are only temporary. The only lasting thing is self motivation. – Homer Rice&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Playing Sports Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hard work beats talent when talent doesn’t work hard. – Tim Notke&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Never say never because limits, like fears, are often just an illusion. – Michael Jordan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without self-discipline, success is impossible, period. – Lou Holtz&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strength does not come from physical capacity. It comes from an indomitable will. – Mahatma Gandhi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I became a good pitcher when I stopped trying to make them miss the ball and started trying to make them hit it. – Sandy Koufax&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you know what my favorite part of the game is? The opportunity to play. – Mike Singletary&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Success is where preparation and opportunity meet. – Bobby Unser&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is more difficult to stay on top than to get there. – Mia Hamm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Age is no barrier. It's a limitation you put on your mind. – Jackie Joyner-Kersee&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may encounter many defeats but we must not be defeated. – Maya Angelou&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Sports Lover Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stubbornness usually is considered a negative; but I think that trait has been a positive for me.- Cal Ripken, Jr.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do not let what you can not do interfere with what you can do. – John Wooden&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not the will to win that matters — everyone has that. It’s the will to prepare to win that matters. – Paul “Bear” Bryant&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An athlete cannot run with money in his pockets. He must run with hope in his heart and dreams in his head. – Emil Zatopek&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your talent is God’s gift to you. What you do with it is your gift back to God. – Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Sports Quotes About Winning&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The will to win is important, but the will to prepare is vital. – Joe Paterno&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not the will to win that matters — everyone has that. It’s the will to prepare to win that matters. – Paul “Bear” Bryant&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve failed over and over and over again in my life. And that is why I succeed. – Michael Jordan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A champion is someone who gets up when he can’t. – Jack Dempsey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It isn’t the mountains ahead to climb that wear you out; it’s the pebble in your shoe. – Muhammad Ali&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Always make a total effort, even when the odds are against you. – Arnold Palmer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If a team wants to intimidate you physically and you let them, they’ve won. – Mia Hamm&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The difference between the impossible and the possible lies in a person's determination. – Tommy Lasorda&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Sports Quotes About Confidence&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Run when you can, walk if you have to, crawl if you must; just never give up. – Dean Karnazes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winning isn’t everything, but wanting to win is. – Vince Lombardi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you’ve got something to prove, there’s nothing greater than a challenge. – Terry Bradshaw&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you can believe it, the mind can achieve it. – Ronnie Lott&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sports do not build character. They reveal it. – Heywood Broun&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have to be at your strongest when you’re feeling at your weakest. – Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Sports Quotes Failure&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve failed over and over again in my life. And that is why I succeed. – Michael Jordan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you fail to prepare, you’re prepared to fail. – Mark Spitz&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You miss 100 percent of the shots you don’t take. – Wayne Gretzky&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winners never quit and quitters never win. – Vince Lombardi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What makes something special is not just what you have to gain, but what you feel there is to lose. – Andre Agassi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are afraid of failure you don’t deserve to be successful! – Charles Barkley&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Persistence can change failure into extraordinary achievement. – Matt Biondi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Sports Quotes Short&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make each day your masterpiece. – John Wooden&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It never gets easier. You just get better. – Jordan Hoechlin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It ain’t over ’til it’s over. – Yogi Berra&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You’re never a loser until you quit trying. – Mike Ditka&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Success trains. Failure complains. – Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/love-football-quotes.html"&gt;Next&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="sports"></category><category term="sports"></category><category term="quotes"></category><category term="motivation"></category></entry><entry><title>20+ love for football quotes</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/love-football-quotes.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-11-05T14:05:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-11-05T14:05:00+05:30</updated><author><name>8kplays</name></author><id>tag:8kplays.ml,2020-11-05:/love-football-quotes.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Some people think football as a sport. But it's much more than that. In our life You need to look, you need to think, you need to move, you need to find space, you need to help others. Same goes to Football. Below you get some quotes to express your …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Some people think football as a sport. But it's much more than that. In our life You need to look, you need to think, you need to move, you need to find space, you need to help others. Same goes to Football. Below you get some quotes to express your love for football. Share them with your friends and families.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some people think football is a matter of life and death. I assure you, it's much more serious than that. - Bill Shankly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I once cried because i had no shoes to play football, with my friends, but one day i saw a man who had no feet, and i realized how rich i am. - Zinedine zidane&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Football is a game of mistakes. Whoever makes the fewest mistakes wins. - Johan Cruyff&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whenever you enjoy it, you always play the best football. - Karen Carney&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Football is unconditional love. - Tom Brady&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I learnt All about life with a ball at my feet. - ronaldinho&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Playing with your feet is one thing. Play with your heart is another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Football is God's gift to humanity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In football, everything is possible, from the moment you work and you believe in your qualities. - Kylian Mbappe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's two times of year for me: Football season, and waiting for football season. Darius Rucker&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Football Quotes Motivational&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Football was always my dream. I started playing at the age of five, and I'm still playing now. - Sadio Mane&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Loyalty is a big part of football, and it shows if you are a real man or not. - Jack Wilshere&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm very proud because, all my life, I worked very hard to be a football player. - Fabio Cannavaro&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Football's always been cerebral. The most important thing is thinking fast. - Thiago Alcantara&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Football is a team sport and not an individual sport. We win as a team, and every individual is better if we are part of the team. - Fernando Torres&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In football, the worst things are excuses. Excuses mean you cannot grow or move forward. - Pep Guardiola&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Football Quotes Inspirational&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Football runs in my blood, and I did really want to play football. - Radamel Falcao&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To me it was never about what I accomplished on the football field, it was about the way I played the game. Jerry Rice&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not a dreamer. I am a football romantic. - Jurgen Klopp&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's like everything in football - and life. You need to look, you need to think, you need to move, you need to find space, you need to help others. It's very simple in the end. - Johan Cruyff&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Football is a fertility festival. Eleven sperm trying to get into the egg. I feel sorry for the goalkeeper. Bjork&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/hiking-quotes-to-motivated.html"&gt;Next&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="football"></category><category term="football"></category><category term="love"></category></entry><entry><title>Hiking Quotes to Stay Motivated on Your Journey</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/hiking-quotes-to-motivated.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-10-29T18:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-29T18:20:00+05:30</updated><author><name>8kplays</name></author><id>tag:8kplays.ml,2020-10-29:/hiking-quotes-to-motivated.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The best thing about hiking is we come to mountains and nature. We leave all the noise and pollution to feel the happiness. Here are the some hiking quotes to stay motivated on your journey and inspire your to hiking more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Motivational Hiking Quotes for Keep Going&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The best thing about hiking is we come to mountains and nature. We leave all the noise and pollution to feel the happiness. Here are the some hiking quotes to stay motivated on your journey and inspire your to hiking more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Motivational Hiking Quotes for Keep Going&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re going through hell, keep going. – Winston Churchill&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had once again proven that again alone, I was again enough. – Aspen Matis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For hiking is one of those things that you can only do when you have the determination in you. – Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you fell down yesterday, stand up today. – H. G. Wells&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be miserable. Or motivate yourself. Whatever has to be done, it’s always your choice. – Wayne Dyer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Optimism is the faith that leads to achievement. Nothing can be done without hope and confidence – Helen Keller&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would never have started this trip if I had known how tough it was, but I couldn’t and wouldn’t quit – Ben Montgomery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Best Hiking Quotes with Friends&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speed is not a priority, just enjoy your hike – Keep smile. – Barry Perdana Putra&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You need mountains, long staircases don’t make good hikers. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Traveling shouldn’t be just a tour, it should be a tale. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Travel teaches as much as a teacher. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountains make me believe that nothing can be bigger than nature, not even human ego. – Jay Kumar Singh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every mountain has its soul… if the mountain does not accept you &amp;amp; you don’t submit to her will, she will destroy you. – Bernadette McDonald&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Returning home is the most difficult part of long-distance hiking; You have grown outside the puzzle and your piece no longer fits. – Cindy Ross&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love going out of my way, beyond what I know, and finding my way back a few extra miles, by another trail, with a compass that argues with the map…nights alone in motels in remote western towns where I know no one and no one I know knows where I am, nights with strange paintings and floral spreads and cable television that furnish a reprieve from my own biography, when in Benjamin’s terms, I have lost myself though I know where I am. Moments when I say to myself as feet or car clear a crest or round a bend, I have never seen this place before. Times when some architectural detail on vista that has escaped me these many years says to me that I never did know where I was, even when I was home. – Rebecca Solnit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting to the top is optional. Getting down is mandatory. – Ed Viesturs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;None of your knowledge, your reading, your connections will be of any use here: two legs suffice, and big eyes to see with. Walk alone, across mountains or through forests. You are nobody to the hills or the thick boughs heavy with greenery. You are no longer a role, or a status, not even an individual, but a body, a body that feels sharp stones on the paths, the caress of long grass and the freshness of the wind. When you walk, the world has neither present nor future: nothing but the cycle of mornings and evenings. Always the same thing to do all day: walk. But the walker who marvels while walking (the blue of the rocks in a July evening light, the silvery green of olive leaves at noon, the violet morning hills) has no past, no plans, no experience. He has within him the eternal child. While walking I am but a simple gaze. – Frédéric Gros&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You need mountains, long staircases don’t make good hikers. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hiking—much like drinking—is something that sounds more fun to the uninitiated than it actually is. – Mindy McGinnis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love writing in the sunshine ’till my head throbs and hiking in the woods ’till my feet hurt. – Kaylee Stepkoski&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Hiking Quotes for Couples&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You need special shoes for hiking—and a bit of a special soul as well. – Terri Guillemets&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The will to succeed is important, but what’s more important is the will to prepare. – Bobby Knight&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nature is not a place to visit. It is home. – Gary Snyder&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not the mountain we conquer, but ourselves. – Sir Edmund Hillary&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do the difficult things while they are easy and do the great things while they are small. A journey of a thousand miles must begin with a single step. – Lao Tzu&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Hiking Quotes for Instagram&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountains are freedom. Treat them respectfully. – Conrad Anker&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It does not matter how slowly you go as long as you do not stop. – Confucius&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do something wonderful, people may imitate it. – Albert Schweitzer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;May your dreams be larger than mountains and may you have the courage to scale their summits. – Harley King&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the mountain that has been calling me, and it’s time to answer. – Susan Jagannath&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is always an adventure waiting in the woods. – Katelyn S. Bolds&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may encounter many defeats but we must not be defeated. – Maya Angelou&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hiking is the only slightly less ugly stepsister of running. – Lindy Hughes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Short Hiking Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best view comes after the hardest climb. – Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The world reveals itself to those who travel on foot. – Werner Herzog&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did it. I said I’d do it and I’ve done it. – Ben Montgomery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you reach the end of your rope, tie a knot in it and hang on. – Franklin D. Roosevelt&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It always seems impossible until it’s done. – Nelson Mandela&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trekking means a travelling experience with a thrilling excitement. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be a true traveler, don’t be a temporary tourist. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hike your own hike to health. – Harken Headers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feeling LOW? – Prajakta Mhadnak&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The secret of getting ahead is getting started. – Mark Twain&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/cricket-quotes-to-motivate-you.html"&gt;Next&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="hiking"></category><category term="hiking"></category><category term="trekking"></category><category term="quotes"></category><category term="motivation"></category><category term="friends"></category></entry><entry><title>30+ Cricket Quotes to Motivate You</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/cricket-quotes-to-motivate-you.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-10-26T10:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-26T10:20:00+05:30</updated><author><name>8kplays</name></author><id>tag:8kplays.ml,2020-10-26:/cricket-quotes-to-motivate-you.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;When it’s time to name the most excited sports then cricket is one of them. Because in cricket one ball can decide which team is going to win. We can’t guess what happen on the second ball. When you are playing in the field with thousands of people …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;When it’s time to name the most excited sports then cricket is one of them. Because in cricket one ball can decide which team is going to win. We can’t guess what happen on the second ball. When you are playing in the field with thousands of people crowd around you cheering up, then you have to stay motivate you and keep your focus in the match. Below you can find some cricket quotes to motivate you when match is not on your side. To motivate and inspire you to give your best that you can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;quotes for cricket&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cricket as a passion is distinctly contagious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cricket to us was more than play, It was a worship in the summer sun. – Edmund Blunden&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Actually nobody can be perfect in cricket. Everybody makes mistakes. It is important to learn from your mistakes and correct them. – Kumar Sangakkara&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My job is to perform, enjoy cricket and thank God for whatever he has given me. – Suresh Raina&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cricket is battle and service and sport and art. – Douglas Jardine&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The true test of any cricketer’s character is how he reacts when the going gets tough, when it’s time to dig in. – Michael Holding&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;cricket love quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To me, Cricket is a simple game. Keep it simple and just go out and play. – Shane Warne&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Concentration’s like a shower, you don’t turn it on until you want to bathe. That was cricket for me. – Sir Garfield Sobers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every morning I woke up, I believed that I could score runs for India. – Sourav Ganguly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cricket is the most important thing to me, so rest pales in comparison. – Virat Kohli&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The joy of doing well as a batsman for your country is much more than that little joy of going for a party and enjoying music. It is a completely different high, and I get high by performances. That’s what I enjoy now. – Virat Kohli&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the game &amp;amp; Chase your dreams. Dreams do come true. – Sachin Tendulkar&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My first bat was shaped of a coconut branch and from that day, all I wanted to do was to be a cricketer. – Brian Lara&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;cricket quotes funny&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m convinced things will go much better if the players smile and have some fun on the field, rather than acting like wound-up spring. – Jonty Rhodes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cricket is the only sport in the world where you are absolutely horrible at something and you still need to go out and do it. – Harsha Bhogle&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;cricket quotes motivational&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t play for the crowd. You play for the country. – Mahendra Singh Dhoni&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You dont win or lose the games because of the 11 you select. You win or lose with that those 11 do on the field. – Rahul Dravid&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If it’s difficult, I will do it now. If it’s impossible, I will do it presently. – Don Bradman&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to do something, achieve something, you can’t be thinking all the time of what you don’t have. – Kapil Dev&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of all, convince yourself that you are the best because the rest of your life is going to go proving this to others. – Wasim Akram&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The key to handling pressure is to enjoy it when you’re confronted with it rather than worry about it too much. – Steve Waugh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Never give up; just absolutely never give up. – Shane Warne&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;cricket quotes for instagram&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every morning I woke up, I believed that I could score runs for India. – Sourav Ganguly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Compromise for your dream but never compromise on your dream. – Imran khan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is far more than a game, this cricket.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re good enough, you don’t need to say anything to win. – Curtly Ambrose&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can cut the tension with a cricket stump&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;cricket quotes inspirational&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have failed at times, but I never stop trying. – Rahul Dravid&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When people throw stones at you, you turn them into milestones. – Sachin Tendulkar&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some folks will say ‘Oh, Winning ain’t all!’ But I know it is all. At the end of the day no one looks at the loser. So that is why we play to win. – Vivian Richards&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A wise man learns by the mistakes of others, a fool by own. – Adam Gilchrist&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have failed more times than I have succeeded, but I never gave up, and will never give up, till my last breath, and that's what cricket has taught me. – Yuvraj Singh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You’re always going to be criticised to a degree. Some people didn’t like Mother Teresa as well. – Brendon McCullum&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/sports-quotes-for-motivation.html"&gt;Next&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="cricket"></category><category term="cricket"></category><category term="quotes"></category><category term="motivation"></category></entry></feed>