<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>8k Plays</title><link href="/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>/</id><updated>2020-10-29T18:20:00+05:30</updated><subtitle>Share Cricket, Football, Sports Motivational and Inspiration Quotes with your friends &amp; family</subtitle><entry><title>Hiking Quotes to Stay Motivated on Your Journey</title><link href="/hiking-quotes-to-motivated.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-10-29T18:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-29T18:20:00+05:30</updated><author><name>8kplays</name></author><id>tag:None,2020-10-29:/hiking-quotes-to-motivated.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The best thing about hiking is we come to mountains and nature. We leave all the noise and pollution to feel the happiness. Here are the some hiking quotes to stay motivated on your journey and inspire your to hiking more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Motivational Hiking Quotes for Keep Going&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The best thing about hiking is we come to mountains and nature. We leave all the noise and pollution to feel the happiness. Here are the some hiking quotes to stay motivated on your journey and inspire your to hiking more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Motivational Hiking Quotes for Keep Going&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re going through hell, keep going. – Winston Churchill&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had once again proven that again alone, I was again enough. – Aspen Matis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For hiking is one of those things that you can only do when you have the determination in you. – Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you fell down yesterday, stand up today. – H. G. Wells&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be miserable. Or motivate yourself. Whatever has to be done, it’s always your choice. – Wayne Dyer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Optimism is the faith that leads to achievement. Nothing can be done without hope and confidence – Helen Keller&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would never have started this trip if I had known how tough it was, but I couldn’t and wouldn’t quit – Ben Montgomery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Best Hiking Quotes with Friends&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speed is not a priority, just enjoy your hike – Keep smile. – Barry Perdana Putra&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You need mountains, long staircases don’t make good hikers. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Traveling shouldn’t be just a tour, it should be a tale. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Travel teaches as much as a teacher. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountains make me believe that nothing can be bigger than nature, not even human ego. – Jay Kumar Singh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every mountain has its soul… if the mountain does not accept you &amp;amp; you don’t submit to her will, she will destroy you. – Bernadette McDonald&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Returning home is the most difficult part of long-distance hiking; You have grown outside the puzzle and your piece no longer fits. – Cindy Ross&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love going out of my way, beyond what I know, and finding my way back a few extra miles, by another trail, with a compass that argues with the map…nights alone in motels in remote western towns where I know no one and no one I know knows where I am, nights with strange paintings and floral spreads and cable television that furnish a reprieve from my own biography, when in Benjamin’s terms, I have lost myself though I know where I am. Moments when I say to myself as feet or car clear a crest or round a bend, I have never seen this place before. Times when some architectural detail on vista that has escaped me these many years says to me that I never did know where I was, even when I was home. – Rebecca Solnit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting to the top is optional. Getting down is mandatory. – Ed Viesturs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;None of your knowledge, your reading, your connections will be of any use here: two legs suffice, and big eyes to see with. Walk alone, across mountains or through forests. You are nobody to the hills or the thick boughs heavy with greenery. You are no longer a role, or a status, not even an individual, but a body, a body that feels sharp stones on the paths, the caress of long grass and the freshness of the wind. When you walk, the world has neither present nor future: nothing but the cycle of mornings and evenings. Always the same thing to do all day: walk. But the walker who marvels while walking (the blue of the rocks in a July evening light, the silvery green of olive leaves at noon, the violet morning hills) has no past, no plans, no experience. He has within him the eternal child. While walking I am but a simple gaze. – Frédéric Gros&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You need mountains, long staircases don’t make good hikers. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hiking—much like drinking—is something that sounds more fun to the uninitiated than it actually is. – Mindy McGinnis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love writing in the sunshine ’till my head throbs and hiking in the woods ’till my feet hurt. – Kaylee Stepkoski&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Hiking Quotes for Couples&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You need special shoes for hiking—and a bit of a special soul as well. – Terri Guillemets&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The will to succeed is important, but what’s more important is the will to prepare. – Bobby Knight&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nature is not a place to visit. It is home. – Gary Snyder&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not the mountain we conquer, but ourselves. – Sir Edmund Hillary&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do the difficult things while they are easy and do the great things while they are small. A journey of a thousand miles must begin with a single step. – Lao Tzu&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Hiking Quotes for Instagram&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountains are freedom. Treat them respectfully. – Conrad Anker&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It does not matter how slowly you go as long as you do not stop. – Confucius&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do something wonderful, people may imitate it. – Albert Schweitzer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;May your dreams be larger than mountains and may you have the courage to scale their summits. – Harley King&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the mountain that has been calling me, and it’s time to answer. – Susan Jagannath&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is always an adventure waiting in the woods. – Katelyn S. Bolds&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may encounter many defeats but we must not be defeated. – Maya Angelou&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hiking is the only slightly less ugly stepsister of running. – Lindy Hughes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Short Hiking Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best view comes after the hardest climb. – Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The world reveals itself to those who travel on foot. – Werner Herzog&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did it. I said I’d do it and I’ve done it. – Ben Montgomery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you reach the end of your rope, tie a knot in it and hang on. – Franklin D. Roosevelt&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It always seems impossible until it’s done. – Nelson Mandela&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trekking means a travelling experience with a thrilling excitement. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be a true traveler, don’t be a temporary tourist. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hike your own hike to health. – Harken Headers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feeling LOW? – Prajakta Mhadnak&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The secret of getting ahead is getting started. – Mark Twain&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><category term="hiking"></category><category term="hiking"></category><category term="trekking"></category><category term="quotes"></category><category term="motivation"></category><category term="friends"></category></entry><entry><title>30+ Cricket Quotes to Motivate You</title><link href="/cricket-quotes-to-motivate-you.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-10-26T10:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-26T10:20:00+05:30</updated><author><name>8kplays</name></author><id>tag:None,2020-10-26:/cricket-quotes-to-motivate-you.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;When it’s time to name the most excited sports then cricket is one of them. Because in cricket one ball can decide which team is going to win. We can’t guess what happen on the second ball. When you are playing in the field with thousands of people …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;When it’s time to name the most excited sports then cricket is one of them. Because in cricket one ball can decide which team is going to win. We can’t guess what happen on the second ball. When you are playing in the field with thousands of people crowd around you cheering up, then you have to stay motivate you and keep your focus in the match. Below you can find some cricket quotes to motivate you when match is not on your side. To motivate and inspire you to give your best that you can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;quotes for cricket&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cricket as a passion is distinctly contagious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cricket to us was more than play, It was a worship in the summer sun. – Edmund Blunden&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Actually nobody can be perfect in cricket. Everybody makes mistakes. It is important to learn from your mistakes and correct them. – Kumar Sangakkara&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My job is to perform, enjoy cricket and thank God for whatever he has given me. – Suresh Raina&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cricket is battle and service and sport and art. – Douglas Jardine&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The true test of any cricketer’s character is how he reacts when the going gets tough, when it’s time to dig in. – Michael Holding&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;cricket love quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To me, Cricket is a simple game. Keep it simple and just go out and play. – Shane Warne&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Concentration’s like a shower, you don’t turn it on until you want to bathe. That was cricket for me. – Sir Garfield Sobers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every morning I woke up, I believed that I could score runs for India. – Sourav Ganguly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cricket is the most important thing to me, so rest pales in comparison. – Virat Kohli&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The joy of doing well as a batsman for your country is much more than that little joy of going for a party and enjoying music. It is a completely different high, and I get high by performances. That’s what I enjoy now. – Virat Kohli&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the game &amp;amp; Chase your dreams. Dreams do come true. – Sachin Tendulkar&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My first bat was shaped of a coconut branch and from that day, all I wanted to do was to be a cricketer. – Brian Lara&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;cricket quotes funny&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m convinced things will go much better if the players smile and have some fun on the field, rather than acting like wound-up spring. – Jonty Rhodes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cricket is the only sport in the world where you are absolutely horrible at something and you still need to go out and do it. – Harsha Bhogle&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;cricket quotes motivational&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t play for the crowd. You play for the country. – Mahendra Singh Dhoni&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You dont win or lose the games because of the 11 you select. You win or lose with that those 11 do on the field. – Rahul Dravid&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If it’s difficult, I will do it now. If it’s impossible, I will do it presently. – Don Bradman&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to do something, achieve something, you can’t be thinking all the time of what you don’t have. – Kapil Dev&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of all, convince yourself that you are the best because the rest of your life is going to go proving this to others. – Wasim Akram&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The key to handling pressure is to enjoy it when you’re confronted with it rather than worry about it too much. – Steve Waugh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Never give up; just absolutely never give up. – Shane Warne&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;cricket quotes for instagram&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every morning I woke up, I believed that I could score runs for India. – Sourav Ganguly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Compromise for your dream but never compromise on your dream. – Imran khan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is far more than a game, this cricket.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re good enough, you don’t need to say anything to win. – Curtly Ambrose&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can cut the tension with a cricket stump&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;cricket quotes inspirational&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have failed at times, but I never stop trying. – Rahul Dravid&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When people throw stones at you, you turn them into milestones. – Sachin Tendulkar&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some folks will say ‘Oh, Winning ain’t all!’ But I know it is all. At the end of the day no one looks at the loser. So that is why we play to win. – Vivian Richards&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A wise man learns by the mistakes of others, a fool by own. – Adam Gilchrist&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have failed more times than I have succeeded, but I never gave up, and will never give up, till my last breath, and that's what cricket has taught me. – Yuvraj Singh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You’re always going to be criticised to a degree. Some people didn’t like Mother Teresa as well. – Brendon McCullum&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><category term="cricket"></category><category term="cricket"></category><category term="quotes"></category><category term="motivation"></category></entry></feed>