<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>8k Plays - archery</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://8kplays.ml/feeds/archery.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://8kplays.ml/</id><updated>2021-01-07T15:23:00+05:30</updated><subtitle>Share your emotions through Quotes</subtitle><entry><title>Famous Archery Quotes You Want To Know</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/archery-quotes.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-01-07T15:23:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-01-07T15:23:00+05:30</updated><author><name>8kplays</name></author><id>tag:8kplays.ml,2021-01-07:/archery-quotes.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Archery is not just a bow and arrow. It is much more than that. It's as old as mankind. It teaches us to be the focus and patient in our life. Below you can find some famous archery quotes to inspire you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Archery Inspirational Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The history of the bow …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Archery is not just a bow and arrow. It is much more than that. It's as old as mankind. It teaches us to be the focus and patient in our life. Below you can find some famous archery quotes to inspire you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Archery Inspirational Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The history of the bow and arrow is the history of mankind. - Fred Bear&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Archery does not get difficult or hard to understand until the arrow misses. - Milan E. Elott&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A good archer is known not by his arrows but by his aim. - Thomas Fuller&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The worst thing is to try to shoot as well as your previous shot. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Archery is a feeling you can’t explain. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not about being the best. It’s about being better than you were yesterday. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But you must be patient and careful; nor should you expect to become an accomplished archer without long and severe training. - Maurice Thompson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The archer that shoots badly has a lie ready. - Spanish Proverb&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing clears a troubled mind better than shooting a bow. - Fred Bear&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have to relax when you’re shooting an arrow. You can’t be tense. And that just helps, in your day-to-day life. - Stephen Amell&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you are a beginning, intermediate, or even advanced archer, Archery will give you something that’s almost impossible to find elsewhere. - Usa Archery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other archers are not my competition. I stand with them, not against them. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An arrow is never afraid of shooting from the bow; but it is afraid of not reaching the target! - Mehmet Murat ildan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even as the archer loves the arrow that flies, so too he loves the bow that remains constant in his hands. - Nigerian Proverb&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I shoot an arrow into the air, where it lands I do not care: I get my arrows wholesale! - Curly Howard&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Short Archery Quotes for Instagram&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Draw not your bow till your arrow is fixed. - English Proverbs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the long run, you only hit what you aim at. - Henry Thoreau&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t wear bows. I shoot them. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Archery requires very sensitive muscles. - Im Dong-Hyun&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No shot is hard to make, it’s just easier to miss. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Forget the last arrow only the next will count. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don’t shoot you don’t understand. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Archery is not just a sports. Its a life skill. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep Calm and Shoot Straight. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no excellence in archery without great labour. - Maurice Thompson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An archer cannot hit the bullseye if he doesn’t know where the target is. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don’t shoot fast. Shoot good. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/swimming-quotes.html"&gt;Next&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="archery"></category><category term="archery"></category><category term="quotes"></category></entry></feed>