<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>8k Plays - badminton</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://8kplays.ml/feeds/badminton.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://8kplays.ml/</id><updated>2021-01-08T12:45:00+05:30</updated><subtitle>Share your emotions through Quotes</subtitle><entry><title>Inspiring Badminton Quotes : Inspirational, Motivational and Instagram</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/badminton-quotes.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-01-08T12:45:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-01-08T12:45:00+05:30</updated><author><name>8kplays</name></author><id>tag:8kplays.ml,2021-01-08:/badminton-quotes.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Best motivational and Inspirational Badminton quotes. To inspire you for it. Share them on Instagram or with your friends. These quotes will motivate you for your goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Quotes About Badminton&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A champion has to be disciplined by practicing regularly in the right manner, respect coaches and most importantly ought to …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Best motivational and Inspirational Badminton quotes. To inspire you for it. Share them on Instagram or with your friends. These quotes will motivate you for your goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Quotes About Badminton&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A champion has to be disciplined by practicing regularly in the right manner, respect coaches and most importantly ought to have self-belief. - Saina Nehwal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Badminton is like ballet dancing. It requires a lot of control, strength, mind play and measured movement. - Aamir Khan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who play badminton well take decisions quickly. - Dmitry Medvedev&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only a shuttler knows how demanding the fastest sport in the world is. - Tiyasha&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your dream will always defeat reality if you give it chance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ability is what you’re capable of doing. Motivation determines what you do. Attitude determines how well you do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Discipline is the bridge between your badminton goals and badminton success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your dream will always defeat reality if you give it chance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Badminton Love Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I am playing badminton there are only two people in the world, myself and my opponent. - Erland Kops&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choosing a badminton goal and sticking to it changes everything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When badminton was accepted into the Barcelona Olympic Games it showed that there was an acceptance of my sport internationally. - Rhonda Cator&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would say that it is the explosiveness that I possess in my game. Like a crouching tiger waiting to pounce on it preys. - Lee Chong Wei&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In badminton, they use a lot from the wrist. But I use a lot from the shoulder. - Li Na&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Badminton Quotes For Instagram&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Life is a game, Badminton is serious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep calm and play badminton.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If we dare to win, we should also dare to lose. - Lee Chong Wei&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not the hours you put in….it’s what you put in those hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Talk with your racquet, play with your heart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Champions keep playing until they get it right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you fast enough to handle a badminton shuttle?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Badminton: Too Fast too Furious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Badminton is not as glamorous as cricket. - Saina Nehwal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hit me with your best shot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hustle and hit and never quit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/archery-quotes.html"&gt;Next&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="badminton"></category><category term="badminton"></category><category term="quotes"></category></entry></feed>