<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>8k Plays - basketball</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://8kplays.ml/feeds/basketball.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://8kplays.ml/</id><updated>2021-01-09T14:01:00+05:30</updated><subtitle>Share your emotions through Quotes</subtitle><entry><title>60+ Basketball Quotes That Will Motivate You To Keep Trying</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/basketball-quotes.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-01-09T14:01:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-01-09T14:01:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Deepak</name></author><id>tag:8kplays.ml,2021-01-09:/basketball-quotes.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Looking for popular Basketball quotes by famous players to motivate you to get to your goals. These quotes about life, dream, attitude, failure, keep practice and playing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also see: 
&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/sports-quotes-for-motivation.html"&gt;Motivation Sports Quotes&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/hiking-quotes-to-motivated.html"&gt;Hiking Quotes to stay motivated&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no such thing as a perfect basketball player, and I don …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Looking for popular Basketball quotes by famous players to motivate you to get to your goals. These quotes about life, dream, attitude, failure, keep practice and playing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also see: 
&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/sports-quotes-for-motivation.html"&gt;Motivation Sports Quotes&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/hiking-quotes-to-motivated.html"&gt;Hiking Quotes to stay motivated&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no such thing as a perfect basketball player, and I don’t believe there is only one greatest player either. -  Michael Jordan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Basketball is a lifelong game. You continue to learn from the game day in and day out, and all along the way, you get better. - Scottie Pippen&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ask not what your teammates can do for you. Ask what you can do for your teammates. - Magic Johnson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ability may get you to the top, but it takes character to keep you there. - John Wooden&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I gave everything I had to basketball. The passion is still there, but the desire to play is not. It was a great ride. - Allen Iverson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Great players are willing to give up their own personal achievement for the achievement of the group. It enhances everybody. - Kareem Abdul-Jabbar&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is a lot of basketball beyond our control, but a player should never let anyone try harder than he does. - Dean Smith&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once you are labeled the best you want to stay up there, and you can’t do it by loafing around. If I don’t keep changing, I’m history. - Larry Bird&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create unselfishness as the most important team attribute. - Bill Russell&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing is given. Everything is earned. - LeBron James&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can’t get much done in life if you only work on the days when you feel good. - Jerry West&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you’re not practicing, someone else is getting better. - Allen Iverson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Push yourself again and again. Don’t give an inch until the final buzzer sounds. - Larry Bird&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What do you do with a mistake: recognize it, admit it, learn from it, forget it. - Dean Smith&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Basketball Quotes by Players&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are some more quotes by famous football players that encourage us to never accept our failure and keep trying until we get what we want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Michael Jordan&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Always turn a negative situation into a positive situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can accept failure, everyone fails at something. But I can't accept not trying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Talent wins games, but teamwork and intelligence wins championships.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've always believed that if you put in the work, the results will come.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've missed more than 9000 shots in my career. I've lost almost 300 games. 26 times, I've been trusted to take the game winning shot and missed. I've failed over and over and over again in my life. And that is why I succeed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some people want it to happen, some wish it would happen, others make it happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no 'i' in team but there is in win.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just play. Have fun. Enjoy the game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To be successful you have to be selfish, or else you never achieve. And once you get to your highest level, then you have to be unselfish. Stay reachable. Stay in touch. Don't isolate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In reality, I never want to grow up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As athletes, we're used to reacting quickly. Here, it's 'come, stop, come, stop.' There's a lot of downtime. That's the toughest part of the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I won't have any competitive instincts in any sports, other than golf. I can't see being competitive in sports any more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wasn't really a work-conscious type of person. I was a player. I loved to play sports.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Kobe Bryant&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're afraid to fail, then you're probably going to fail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have self-doubt. I have insecurity. I have fear of failure. I have nights when I show up at the arena and I'm like, 'My back hurts, my feet hurt, my knees hurt. I don't have it. I just want to chill.' We all have self-doubt. You don't deny it, but you also don't capitulate to it. You embrace it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winning takes precedence over all. There's no gray area. No almosts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People just don't understand how obsessed I am with winning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;LeBron James&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I treated it like every day was my last day with a basketball.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Basketball is my passion, I love it. But my family and friends mean everything to me. That's what's important. I need my phone so I can keep in contact with them at all times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I played football for a team called the East Dragons on the east side of town. We only had six regular season games. And six games I played tail back and I had 18 touchdowns in six games. That's when I knew I had some athletic ability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's always a struggle growing up in Akron.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If a great opportunity opens itself up, I would love to be involved... or star in a movie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm confident with my ability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Stephen Curry&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's crazy how fast you get out of shape if you miss a couple days of action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know the blessing of having a dad who played 16 years in the league. That experience, and seeing him as an example, let me know that it's possible. It's not easy, but it's possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I step forward on the floor, I have the confidence that I'm the best player playing that night and that I am the most prepared at what I need to be doing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know what I do for my team and what my teammates expect of me on both ends of the floor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In college, a loss is pretty devastating. That feeling kind of goes away in an 82-game season. You hate to lose, but you also have a lot more games to make up for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I always have confidence, whether I miss four in a row or make four in a row, that the next one's going in. To a coach, sometimes that might not make sense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of the stuff I try in a game, in the moment, I have supreme confidence I'm going to execute it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To be able to finish opportunities that I do get in the paint, that makes a difference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Basketball is booming, and it's not just an Under Armour standpoint: it's about the game itself. Kids going out and playing and being inspired by what we do on the court.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's a reason that I have confidence out there, and it's about how I prepare for games and for series and seasons and whatnot, so we've got to stick with that kind of thought process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Derrick Rose&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hard part that I had to go through in life, period, is living in poverty and not being able to get what I want.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My mom is real passionate and a family-first woman. She always told me that just because I can shoot a basketball better than someone else, I shouldn't think that I'm better than them. I know if I change, my friends and family would lay me down. She just wants to see her kids do right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My days shouldn't be hard because I'm doing what I'm doing and that's playing basketball.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Basketball Quotes for Instagram&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some wish for it, we work for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can’t control the minutes you play, but you can control how you play the minutes you get.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you ain’t hurting, you ain’t playing hard enough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nobody trains to be backup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you feel like quitting, think about why you started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Teamwork makes the dream work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Basketball doesn’t build character. It reveals it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winners don’t wait for chances, they take them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Winners train; losers complain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Play til the clock says 0:00&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All things are difficult before they are easy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One spirit, one team, one win.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Defend until the end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All’s fair in love and basketball – Love &amp;amp; Basketball.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/badminton-quotes.html"&gt;Next&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="basketball"></category><category term="basketball"></category><category term="quotes"></category></entry></feed>