<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>8k Plays - corona</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://8kplays.ml/feeds/corona.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://8kplays.ml/</id><updated>2021-01-11T12:55:00+05:30</updated><subtitle>Share your emotions through Quotes</subtitle><entry><title>30+ Corona Quotes To Make You Feel Positive</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/corona-quotes.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-01-11T12:55:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-01-11T12:55:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Deepak</name></author><id>tag:8kplays.ml,2021-01-11:/corona-quotes.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Coronavirus changed our lives like we never thought and affects all people. There are corona quotes that will help you to change your negativity to positivity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also see: 
&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/cricket-quotes-to-motivate-you.html"&gt;Cricket Quotes&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/sports-quotes-for-motivation.html"&gt;Motivational Sports Quotes &lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some young people think they're invincible - this virus definitely does affect people my age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The danger which …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Coronavirus changed our lives like we never thought and affects all people. There are corona quotes that will help you to change your negativity to positivity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also see: 
&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/cricket-quotes-to-motivate-you.html"&gt;Cricket Quotes&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/sports-quotes-for-motivation.html"&gt;Motivational Sports Quotes &lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some young people think they're invincible - this virus definitely does affect people my age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The danger which is least expected soonest comes to us. - Voltaire&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The safety of the people shall be the highest law. Marcus Tullius Cicero&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I seriously can't wait for the day where they announce that coronavirus is gone and we can all go back to normal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;COVID-19 will reshape our world. We don't yet know when the crisis will end. But we can be sure that by the time it does, our world will look very different. - Josep Borrell&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing is of greater importance than the conservation of human life. - Former U.S. President Calvin Coolidge&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tough times never last, tough people do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for putting yourself in the way of danger to save others, to save the public. This is what it means to be a hero. This is what it means to build a beautiful legacy. Thank you for everything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Corona Quotes for Safety&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let's stay at home be safe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay home don't panic, beat the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay at home if you have a high temperature and a cough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay home stay safe &amp;amp; wash your hands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is nothing that gives more assurance than a Mask. - Colette&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Corona Quotes for Instagram&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everything will be ok&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can Beat if Together&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make corona our reset button&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While we are panicking about COVID-19, Mother earth is healing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to live I stay Home&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stay positive&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Coronavirus Lockdown Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7 Days of Social Distancing: Struck up a conversation with a spider today. Seems nice. He's a web designer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When this quarantine is over, lets not tell some people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mom, this cocial distancing thing is awesome. I don't have to wear pants at all this month!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Coronavirus Quotes Funny&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm not buying a 2021 planner until i see a trailer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually, everyone will be quarantined to their houses with no sports to watch...and in 9 months from now, a boom of babies will be born...and we will call them Coronials.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It took a pandemic to make people realize that the only solution to any problem is avoiding people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don't you hate how you can be sleepy and then not be able to go to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Corona Virus has a very big egi. It will not Come to your house unless you go out and Invite it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is there realy anything new in this New Year???&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wake me up when Corona ends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I SWEAR, we are fighting two pandemics: Coronavirus and Stupidity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Corona virus won't last long because it was made in China.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/failure-quotes.html"&gt;Next&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="corona"></category><category term="corona"></category><category term="quotes"></category></entry></feed>