<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>8k Plays - cricket</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://8kplays.ml/feeds/cricket.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://8kplays.ml/</id><updated>2020-10-26T10:20:00+05:30</updated><subtitle>Share your emotions through Quotes</subtitle><entry><title>30+ Cricket Quotes to Motivate You</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/cricket-quotes-to-motivate-you.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-10-26T10:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-26T10:20:00+05:30</updated><author><name>8kplays</name></author><id>tag:8kplays.ml,2020-10-26:/cricket-quotes-to-motivate-you.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;When it’s time to name the most excited sports then cricket is one of them. Because in cricket one ball can decide which team is going to win. We can’t guess what happen on the second ball. When you are playing in the field with thousands of people …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;When it’s time to name the most excited sports then cricket is one of them. Because in cricket one ball can decide which team is going to win. We can’t guess what happen on the second ball. When you are playing in the field with thousands of people crowd around you cheering up, then you have to stay motivate you and keep your focus in the match. Below you can find some cricket quotes to motivate you when match is not on your side. To motivate and inspire you to give your best that you can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Quotes For Cricket&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cricket as a passion is distinctly contagious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cricket to us was more than play, It was a worship in the summer sun. – Edmund Blunden&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Actually nobody can be perfect in cricket. Everybody makes mistakes. It is important to learn from your mistakes and correct them. – Kumar Sangakkara&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My job is to perform, enjoy cricket and thank God for whatever he has given me. – Suresh Raina&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cricket is battle and service and sport and art. – Douglas Jardine&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The true test of any cricketer’s character is how he reacts when the going gets tough, when it’s time to dig in. – Michael Holding&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Cricket Love Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To me, Cricket is a simple game. Keep it simple and just go out and play. – Shane Warne&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Concentration’s like a shower, you don’t turn it on until you want to bathe. That was cricket for me. – Sir Garfield Sobers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every morning I woke up, I believed that I could score runs for India. – Sourav Ganguly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cricket is the most important thing to me, so rest pales in comparison. – Virat Kohli&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The joy of doing well as a batsman for your country is much more than that little joy of going for a party and enjoying music. It is a completely different high, and I get high by performances. That’s what I enjoy now. – Virat Kohli&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the game &amp;amp; Chase your dreams. Dreams do come true. – Sachin Tendulkar&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My first bat was shaped of a coconut branch and from that day, all I wanted to do was to be a cricketer. – Brian Lara&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Cricket Quotes Funny&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m convinced things will go much better if the players smile and have some fun on the field, rather than acting like wound-up spring. – Jonty Rhodes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cricket is the only sport in the world where you are absolutely horrible at something and you still need to go out and do it. – Harsha Bhogle&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Cricket Quotes Motivational&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t play for the crowd. You play for the country. – Mahendra Singh Dhoni&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You dont win or lose the games because of the 11 you select. You win or lose with that those 11 do on the field. – Rahul Dravid&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If it’s difficult, I will do it now. If it’s impossible, I will do it presently. – Don Bradman&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to do something, achieve something, you can’t be thinking all the time of what you don’t have. – Kapil Dev&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of all, convince yourself that you are the best because the rest of your life is going to go proving this to others. – Wasim Akram&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The key to handling pressure is to enjoy it when you’re confronted with it rather than worry about it too much. – Steve Waugh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Never give up; just absolutely never give up. – Shane Warne&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Cricket Quotes For Instagram&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every morning I woke up, I believed that I could score runs for India. – Sourav Ganguly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Compromise for your dream but never compromise on your dream. – Imran khan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is far more than a game, this cricket.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re good enough, you don’t need to say anything to win. – Curtly Ambrose&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can cut the tension with a cricket stump&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Cricket Quotes Inspirational&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have failed at times, but I never stop trying. – Rahul Dravid&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When people throw stones at you, you turn them into milestones. – Sachin Tendulkar&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some folks will say ‘Oh, Winning ain’t all!’ But I know it is all. At the end of the day no one looks at the loser. So that is why we play to win. – Vivian Richards&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A wise man learns by the mistakes of others, a fool by own. – Adam Gilchrist&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have failed more times than I have succeeded, but I never gave up, and will never give up, till my last breath, and that's what cricket has taught me. – Yuvraj Singh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You’re always going to be criticised to a degree. Some people didn’t like Mother Teresa as well. – Brendon McCullum&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/basketball-quotes.html"&gt;Next&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="cricket"></category><category term="cricket"></category><category term="quotes"></category></entry></feed>