<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>8k Plays - failure</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://8kplays.ml/feeds/failure.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://8kplays.ml/</id><updated>2021-01-10T10:20:00+05:30</updated><subtitle>Share your emotions through Quotes</subtitle><entry><title>60+ Impressive Failure Quotes That Will Change Your Life</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/failure-quotes.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2021-01-10T10:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2021-01-10T10:20:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Deepak</name></author><id>tag:8kplays.ml,2021-01-10:/failure-quotes.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Failure is the most important part of our life. Some peoples accept it and compromise with their life and goals. On the other side, some peoples learn from their failures and keep trying until they get success. There are some motivational failure quotes from famous successful and great peoples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Failure is the most important part of our life. Some peoples accept it and compromise with their life and goals. On the other side, some peoples learn from their failures and keep trying until they get success. There are some motivational failure quotes from famous successful and great peoples.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also see: 
&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/love-football-quotes.html"&gt;Love for Football Quotes&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/badminton-quotes.html"&gt;Inspiring Badminton Quotes &lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you fail, never give up because F.A.I.L. means "first Attempt In Learning" - A.P.J. Abdul Kalam&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pain is temporary. Quitting lasts forever. - Lance Armstrong&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Losers quit when they fail. Winners fail until they succeed. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can accept failure, everyone fails at something. But I can't accept not trying. - Michael Jordan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've missed more than 9000 shots in my career. I've lost almost 300 games. 26 times, I've been trusted to take the game winning shot and missed. I've failed over and over and over again in my life. And that is why I succeed. - Michael Jordan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've failed over and over and over again in my life and that is why I succeed. - Michael Jordan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've never been afraid to fail. - Michael Jordan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have failed at times, but I never stop trying. - Rahul Dravid&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have failed more times than I have succeeded, but I never gave up, and will never give up, till my last breath, and that’s what cricket has taught me. - Yuvraj Singh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every man’s got to figure to get beat sometimes. - Joe Louis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have to fight to reach your dream. You have to sacrifice and work hard for it. - Lionel Messi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no such thing as failure. Failure is just life trying to move us in another direction. - Oprah Winfrey&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is impossible to live without failing at something unless you live so cautiously that you might as well not have lived at all, in which case you have failed by default. - JK Rowling&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Failure is not falling down but refusing to get up. - Chinese proverb&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Failure will never overtake me if my determination to succeed is strong enough. - Og Mandion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The secret of life is to fall seven times and to get up eight times. - Paulo Coelho&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don’t worry about failures, worry about the chances you miss when you don’t even try. - Jack Canfield&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have not failed, I’ve just found 10,000 ways that won’t work. - Thomas Alva Edison&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t learn to walk by following rules. You learn by doing, and by falling over. - Richard Branson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All people fail at certain instances in their lives, the only thing that makes them different is how they manage to stand up or how they choose to fail again. - Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're not prepared to be wrong, you'll never come up with anything original. - Ken Robinson&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Giving up is the only sure way to fail. - Gena Showalter&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Failure should be our teacher, not our undertaker. Failure is delay, not defeat. It is a temporary detour, not a dead end. Failure is something we can avoid only by saying nothing, doing nothing, and being nothing. - Denis Waitley&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Fear of Failure Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you get No as an answer, remember N.O. means "Next Opportunity" - A.P.J. Abdul Kalam&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fear regret more than failure. - Taryn Rose&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is only one thing that makes a dream impossible to achieve: the fear of failure. - Paulo Coelho&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Successful people don’t fear failure but understand that it’s necessary to learn and grow from. - Robert Kiyosaki&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can't be afraid to fail. It's the only way you succeed - you're not gonna succeed all the time, and I know that. - LeBron James&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The topic of leadership is a touchy one. A lot of leaders fail because they don't have the bravery to touch that nerve or strike that chord. Throughout my years, I haven't had that fear. - Kobe Bryant&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're afraid to fail, then you're probably going to fail. - Kobe Bryant&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have self-doubt. I have insecurity. I have fear of failure. I have nights when I show up at the arena and I'm like, 'My back hurts, my feet hurt, my knees hurt. I don't have it. I just want to chill.' We all have self-doubt. You don't deny it, but you also don't capitulate to it. You embrace it. - Kobe Bryant&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Successful Failure Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;End is not the end, if fact E.N.D. means "Effort Never Dies" - A.P.J. Abdul Kalam&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are afraid of failure, you don’t deserve to be successful. - Charles Barkley&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Courage allows the successful woman to fail and learn powerful lessons from the failure. So that in the end, she didn’t fail at all. - Maya Angelou&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Success is most often achieved by those who don't know that failure is inevitable. - Coco Chanel&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Success or failure is caused more by mental attitude than by mental capacity. - Walter Scott&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s fine to celebrate success, but it is more important to heed the lessons of failure. - Bill Gates&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/basketball-quotes.html"&gt;Next&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="failure"></category><category term="failure"></category><category term="quotes"></category></entry></feed>