<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>8k Plays - football</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://8kplays.ml/feeds/football.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://8kplays.ml/</id><updated>2020-11-05T14:05:00+05:30</updated><subtitle>Share your emotions through Quotes</subtitle><entry><title>20+ love for football quotes</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/love-football-quotes.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-11-05T14:05:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-11-05T14:05:00+05:30</updated><author><name>8kplays</name></author><id>tag:8kplays.ml,2020-11-05:/love-football-quotes.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Some people think football as a sport. But it's much more than that. In our life You need to look, you need to think, you need to move, you need to find space, you need to help others. Same goes to Football. Below you get some quotes to express your …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Some people think football as a sport. But it's much more than that. In our life You need to look, you need to think, you need to move, you need to find space, you need to help others. Same goes to Football. Below you get some quotes to express your love for football. Share them with your friends and families.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some people think football is a matter of life and death. I assure you, it's much more serious than that. - Bill Shankly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I once cried because i had no shoes to play football, with my friends, but one day i saw a man who had no feet, and i realized how rich i am. - Zinedine zidane&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Football is a game of mistakes. Whoever makes the fewest mistakes wins. - Johan Cruyff&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whenever you enjoy it, you always play the best football. - Karen Carney&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Football is unconditional love. - Tom Brady&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I learnt All about life with a ball at my feet. - ronaldinho&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Playing with your feet is one thing. Play with your heart is another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Football is God's gift to humanity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In football, everything is possible, from the moment you work and you believe in your qualities. - Kylian Mbappe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's two times of year for me: Football season, and waiting for football season. Darius Rucker&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Football Quotes Motivational&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Football was always my dream. I started playing at the age of five, and I'm still playing now. - Sadio Mane&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Loyalty is a big part of football, and it shows if you are a real man or not. - Jack Wilshere&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm very proud because, all my life, I worked very hard to be a football player. - Fabio Cannavaro&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Football's always been cerebral. The most important thing is thinking fast. - Thiago Alcantara&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Football is a team sport and not an individual sport. We win as a team, and every individual is better if we are part of the team. - Fernando Torres&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In football, the worst things are excuses. Excuses mean you cannot grow or move forward. - Pep Guardiola&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Football Quotes Inspirational&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Football runs in my blood, and I did really want to play football. - Radamel Falcao&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To me it was never about what I accomplished on the football field, it was about the way I played the game. Jerry Rice&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not a dreamer. I am a football romantic. - Jurgen Klopp&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's like everything in football - and life. You need to look, you need to think, you need to move, you need to find space, you need to help others. It's very simple in the end. - Johan Cruyff&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Football is a fertility festival. Eleven sperm trying to get into the egg. I feel sorry for the goalkeeper. Bjork&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a id="next_page" href="https://8kplays.ml/hiking-quotes-to-motivated.html"&gt;Next&lt;a/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><category term="football"></category><category term="football"></category><category term="quotes"></category></entry></feed>