<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>8k Plays - hiking</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://8kplays.ml/feeds/hiking.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://8kplays.ml/</id><updated>2020-10-29T18:20:00+05:30</updated><subtitle>Share Cricket, Football, Sports Motivational and Inspiration Quotes with your friends &amp; family</subtitle><entry><title>Hiking Quotes to Stay Motivated on Your Journey</title><link href="https://8kplays.ml/hiking-quotes-to-motivated.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2020-10-29T18:20:00+05:30</published><updated>2020-10-29T18:20:00+05:30</updated><author><name>8kplays</name></author><id>tag:8kplays.ml,2020-10-29:/hiking-quotes-to-motivated.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The best thing about hiking is we come to mountains and nature. We leave all the noise and pollution to feel the happiness. Here are the some hiking quotes to stay motivated on your journey and inspire your to hiking more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Motivational Hiking Quotes for Keep Going&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The best thing about hiking is we come to mountains and nature. We leave all the noise and pollution to feel the happiness. Here are the some hiking quotes to stay motivated on your journey and inspire your to hiking more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Motivational Hiking Quotes for Keep Going&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re going through hell, keep going. – Winston Churchill&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had once again proven that again alone, I was again enough. – Aspen Matis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For hiking is one of those things that you can only do when you have the determination in you. – Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you fell down yesterday, stand up today. – H. G. Wells&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be miserable. Or motivate yourself. Whatever has to be done, it’s always your choice. – Wayne Dyer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Optimism is the faith that leads to achievement. Nothing can be done without hope and confidence – Helen Keller&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I would never have started this trip if I had known how tough it was, but I couldn’t and wouldn’t quit – Ben Montgomery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Best Hiking Quotes with Friends&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speed is not a priority, just enjoy your hike – Keep smile. – Barry Perdana Putra&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You need mountains, long staircases don’t make good hikers. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Traveling shouldn’t be just a tour, it should be a tale. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Travel teaches as much as a teacher. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountains make me believe that nothing can be bigger than nature, not even human ego. – Jay Kumar Singh&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every mountain has its soul… if the mountain does not accept you &amp;amp; you don’t submit to her will, she will destroy you. – Bernadette McDonald&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Returning home is the most difficult part of long-distance hiking; You have grown outside the puzzle and your piece no longer fits. – Cindy Ross&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love going out of my way, beyond what I know, and finding my way back a few extra miles, by another trail, with a compass that argues with the map…nights alone in motels in remote western towns where I know no one and no one I know knows where I am, nights with strange paintings and floral spreads and cable television that furnish a reprieve from my own biography, when in Benjamin’s terms, I have lost myself though I know where I am. Moments when I say to myself as feet or car clear a crest or round a bend, I have never seen this place before. Times when some architectural detail on vista that has escaped me these many years says to me that I never did know where I was, even when I was home. – Rebecca Solnit&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting to the top is optional. Getting down is mandatory. – Ed Viesturs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;None of your knowledge, your reading, your connections will be of any use here: two legs suffice, and big eyes to see with. Walk alone, across mountains or through forests. You are nobody to the hills or the thick boughs heavy with greenery. You are no longer a role, or a status, not even an individual, but a body, a body that feels sharp stones on the paths, the caress of long grass and the freshness of the wind. When you walk, the world has neither present nor future: nothing but the cycle of mornings and evenings. Always the same thing to do all day: walk. But the walker who marvels while walking (the blue of the rocks in a July evening light, the silvery green of olive leaves at noon, the violet morning hills) has no past, no plans, no experience. He has within him the eternal child. While walking I am but a simple gaze. – Frédéric Gros&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You need mountains, long staircases don’t make good hikers. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hiking—much like drinking—is something that sounds more fun to the uninitiated than it actually is. – Mindy McGinnis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love writing in the sunshine ’till my head throbs and hiking in the woods ’till my feet hurt. – Kaylee Stepkoski&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Hiking Quotes for Couples&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You need special shoes for hiking—and a bit of a special soul as well. – Terri Guillemets&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The will to succeed is important, but what’s more important is the will to prepare. – Bobby Knight&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nature is not a place to visit. It is home. – Gary Snyder&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not the mountain we conquer, but ourselves. – Sir Edmund Hillary&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do the difficult things while they are easy and do the great things while they are small. A journey of a thousand miles must begin with a single step. – Lao Tzu&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Hiking Quotes for Instagram&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mountains are freedom. Treat them respectfully. – Conrad Anker&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It does not matter how slowly you go as long as you do not stop. – Confucius&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do something wonderful, people may imitate it. – Albert Schweitzer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;May your dreams be larger than mountains and may you have the courage to scale their summits. – Harley King&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is the mountain that has been calling me, and it’s time to answer. – Susan Jagannath&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is always an adventure waiting in the woods. – Katelyn S. Bolds&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may encounter many defeats but we must not be defeated. – Maya Angelou&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hiking is the only slightly less ugly stepsister of running. – Lindy Hughes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Short Hiking Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best view comes after the hardest climb. – Unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The world reveals itself to those who travel on foot. – Werner Herzog&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did it. I said I’d do it and I’ve done it. – Ben Montgomery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you reach the end of your rope, tie a knot in it and hang on. – Franklin D. Roosevelt&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It always seems impossible until it’s done. – Nelson Mandela&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trekking means a travelling experience with a thrilling excitement. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be a true traveler, don’t be a temporary tourist. – Amit Kalantri&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hike your own hike to health. – Harken Headers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feeling LOW? – Prajakta Mhadnak&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The secret of getting ahead is getting started. – Mark Twain&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><category term="hiking"></category><category term="hiking"></category><category term="trekking"></category><category term="quotes"></category><category term="motivation"></category><category term="friends"></category></entry></feed>